(Howard:)You ready to talk about it?
(Sheldon:)I'm not nearly drunk enough.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Do you have any idea
what it's like to see
(Sheldon:)your mother ravaging someone?
(Howard:)Does a brisket count?
(Howard:)I'm sorry, buddy, that's rough.
(Howard:)But didn't she know we were coming?
(Sheldon:)No. I wanted to surprise her.
(Sheldon:)What am I supposed to say to
her after something like this?
(Howard:)Well, did she see you
in the window?
(Raj:)-No.
-Then don't say anything.
(Sheldon:)I have to.
(Sheldon:)How can we ever hope to have
a healthy relationship
(Sheldon:)if I don't tell her
how disappointed I am,
(Sheldon:)and that I'll never forgive her?
(Howard:)Well, don't do it on the phone.
(Sheldon:)I'm just going
to tell her I'm coming
(Sheldon:)so she can give that
"Good Time Charlie" the heave-ho.
Thats some tough talk.
I may need to cut you off.